Interviewer: Can you play a musical instrument?
Duncan: I can.
I can play the violin.
Interviewer: How well do you play it?
Duncan: Not very.
Interviewer: Do you have noisy neighbors?
Alice: Yes, I have noisy neighbors.
Interviewer: What do they do?
Alice: My neighbors like to have parties.
Every day and every night.
Interviewer: What’s your favorite month of the year?
Why?
Tiffany: My favorite month is December because it gets colder,
and I like snow and cold weather.
And I like Christmas time.
Interviewer: What kind of music do you like?
Stephen: A lot of kinds of music.
Um, I typically listen to electronic dance, and um, indie rock.
I listen to the new folk, they call it. But I like opera and a lot of jazz.
The list could go on.
Interviewer: What kind of music don’t you like?
Stephen: I don’t like country music.
Interviewer: Do you have a favorite band or singer?
Stephen: Sure.
Right now, my favorite band is Wye Oak from Brooklyn.
Interviewer: What kind of books do you like?
Dasha: Um, I read like all sorts of books, from history books to like, novels,
and all sorts of books, really.
Interviewer: What are you reading at the moment?
Dasha: Uh, at the moment, I’m reading a history of modern France.